[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Rocky movie series, what was family name of Adrian and Rocky?", "correct_answer": "Balboa", "incorrect_answers": ["Davino", "Cipriano", "Corleone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What date was The Crow movie released?", "correct_answer": "May 13, 1994", "incorrect_answers": ["January 13, 1994", "October 15, 1994", "June 6, 1994"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How do fungi reproduce?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Asexually", "By spore dispersal", "Sexually"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to most theories, when was the color pink invented?", "correct_answer": "17th century", "incorrect_answers": ["12th century", "19th century", "15th century"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1995, this 1994 movie won the Oscar for Best Picture at the 67the Academy Awards ceremony.", "correct_answer": "Forrest Gump", "incorrect_answers": ["The Shawshank Redemption", "Four Weddings and a Funeral", "Pulp Fiction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these Mediterranean islands does not belong to the group of the Balearic Islands?", "correct_answer": "Capri", "incorrect_answers": ["Ibiza", "Mallorca", "Formentera"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Bonnie and Clyde at the end of the 1967 movie Bonnie and Clyde?", "correct_answer": "They get killed.", "incorrect_answers": ["They get married.", "They manage to escape once again.", "They get arrested."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the missing number in the following sequence: 6, 18, 36, ___, 216, 648, 1296.", "correct_answer": "108", "incorrect_answers": ["180", "72", "54"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is known as the fear of electricity?", "correct_answer": "Electrophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Eleutherophobia", "Emetophobia", "Enetophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In L. Frank Baums story, The Wonderful Wizard of OZ, the Good Witch of the North comes with the Munchkins to greet Dorothy, and gives her ruby slippers.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Mustard seeds are especially high in this mineral.", "correct_answer": "Phosphorus", "incorrect_answers": ["Potassium", "Sodium", "Iodine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the title of the 1982 film that received the Oscar for Best Picture at the 55th Academy Awards in 1983?", "correct_answer": "Gandhi", "incorrect_answers": ["Tootsie", "E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial", "The Verdict"]}]